# Paula Machado de Souza

Front-End Developer
ppmachado.dev@gmail.com
+55 (34) 99154-5970
Ituiutaba, Minas Gerais - Brazil
github.com/ppmachado

#### **Skills**

- TypeScript (3+ years)
- ReactJS and NextJS (2+ years)
- Storybook and testing. (2+ years)

Other tools I use:

- Git/GitFlow Storybook Styled-Components Ajax AntD Jest Mapbox
- Material UI Rest/GraphQL Figma Adobe XD Sass / Less PWA

#### About me

I'm a front-end developer, based in Brazil but willing to relocate anywhere in the world, with 3 years of web development studies and more than 2 years on-hand working. I'm currently creating a platform, which is aimed to extreme sports enthusiasts, who seek to make friends and map their favorite places to practice around the world, building all design and development. I've also developed innumerous landing pages and websites as a freelance developer.

### IT Experience

Front-End Developer

April 2020 - until today

Building landing pages and small business websites as a freelance developer, working directly on Workana and 99Freelas. Also responsible for the design and development of the Roller Map Company, an entire platform dedicated to skateboarding and roller skaters' enthusiasts.

## **Other Experiences**

• 2019 to 2020 – Video editor and graphic designer (Adobe Premiere, Illustrator and Photoshop)

Working for content creators, some of them with more than 150k followers

Creating thumbs, video editions and subtitles

• 2017 to 2019 – Intern at the Laboratory of Research in Climatology and Water Resources (Federal University of Uberlândia, Brazil)

Working with geoprocessing and satellite analysis about heavy storms in the area

Knowledge of ArcGis and QGis map softwares, creating maps

• 2016 to 2019 – Text translator Portuguese – English

Translating academic texts for students and professors

#### **Education**

• Bachelor and licentiate degree – 2017 to 2022 (incomplete)

Geography – Federal University of Uberlândia (Brazil)

• High School Graduate - 2014

C.E.E.J.A. Padre Moretti (Brazil)

#### Languages

- Portuguese native
- English advanced

Certified at English as a Second Language – 2013

Richmond District School No. 38 (Richmond/BC, Canada)

• Spanish – intermediate